niche-content-packages.com 2016-01-04

# Niche Content Products With Private Label Rights (PLR) - Privacy

Privacy Policy 

If you have any questions about our products or comments about our service we'd love to hear from you! Log a support ticket or if we're online contact us via Live Chat for instant answers at our support page. 

Niche-content-packages.com is committed to protecting the privacy of its online visitors. We will NEVER use your emailaddress and any other personal details we should collect for anything other than to send you the data that you opted in to receive. We will NEVER sell or give your personal information to any third party whatsoever.

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information immediately from our systems. Niche-content-packages.com encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer:

  * Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc.
  * Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.
  * Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated.

Check out the [FTC's site](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/) for more tips on protecting children's privacy online.

Along with a subscription to any of our mailinglists, you agree to receive periodic advertising emails from us. We never send more than one email per day. There will always be an easy to use unsubscribe link at the bottom of every email that you receive, and you may unsubscribe at any time.

We detest "spam". We do not participate in any such underhanded marketing practices and do not condone it in any way.

If you have any further questions or concerns at any time, don't hesitate to contact us via the support page. We'll do our best to get back to you as soon as possible.
